Guide to the Olive Tjaden papers, 1919-1980
Tjaden, Olive papers, 1919-1980
- Series IV. Architectural Plans and Drawings
  - Eblinger residence (Eblinger-Merrit) residence (Job# 497), 1931-03 (Mapcase-folder 33)
  - English garden apartments, 1929-03-25 (Mapcase-folder 33)
  - Unknown residence (Job# 281), Garden City, Long Island, 1929-03-25 (Mapcase-folder 33)
  - Sloan-Dodge residence (Job# 487) (Henry Pierson, builder), 1931-02 (Mapcase-folder 33)
  - Schlossberg residence (Mapcase-folder 33)
  - Hodgson residence (Job# 601), Garden City, Long Island, 1936-06 (Mapcase-folder 34)
  - Whitman residence (Job# 635), Garden City, Long Island, 1937 (Mapcase-folder 34)
  - Alvin Brush residence, Undated (Mapcase-folder 34)
  - Chicken and tool shed, 1935-08 (Mapcase-folder 34)
  - Detail and elevation drawings for Job# 547, 575, 596, and 634, Undated (Mapcase-folder 36)
  - Detail and elevation drawings for Silver residence and Yultide House, Undated (Mapcase-folder 36)
  - Detail and elevation drawings for unknown projects, Undated (Mapcase-folder 36)
  - Apartments, Cedarhurst, Long Island and various unidentified apartment sketches (Mapcase-folder 37)
  - Apartment house (Job #788), January 1940 (Mapcase-folder 37)